&gt;From browsing through the images in the GitHub repo.
من تصفح الصور في GitHub repo.
We wanted you to try your best to answer these two questions.
نرغب في أن تبذل قصارى جهدك للإجابة عن هذين السؤالين.
And don't worry if you didn't get these answers on the first try.
ولا تقلق إذا لم تحصل على هذه الإجابات في المحاولة الأولى.
So first, why are there different drawable folders?
أولاً، لماذا توجد مجلدات مختلفة قابلة للرسم؟
You may have noticed we had the drawable-mdpi folder,
ربما لاحظت أننا لدينا مجلد drawable-mdpi،
the drawable-hdpi folder, the drawable-xhdpi folder, and so on.
ومجلد drawable-hdpi، مجلد drawable-xhdpi، وما إلى ذلك.
Each folder represents a different resolution device.
يمثل كل مجلد جهازًا بدقة شاشة مختلفة.
So remember, resolution means how many pixels are on the screen.
لذا تذكر، أن دقة الشاشة عدد وحدات البكسل الموجودة على الشاشة.
So some of the earlier devices don't have as many pixels.
لذلك فإن بعض الأجهزة القديمة لا تحتوي على العديد من وحدات البكسل.
While the more recent devices have a ton of pixels on screens,
في حين أن الأجهزة الأحدث تحتوي على عدد كبير من وحدات البكسل على الشاشات،
to make the images much sharper.
مما يجعل الصورة أكثر وضوحاً.
So to accommodate for those differences, we have the MDPI folder for
لاستيعاب هذه الاختلافات، لدينا مجلد MDPI
medium density devices, the HDPI folder for high density devices,
للأجهزة متوسطة الكثافة، و مجلد HDPI للأجهزة مرتفعة الكثافة،
and even the XXXHDPI folder, for the extra-extra-extra high density devices.
ومجلد XXXHDPI للأجهزة مرتفع الكثافة جداً جداً جداً.
So the second question is, why there are multiple versions of the same image?
السؤال الثاني، لماذا توجد عدة إصدارات للصورة نفسها؟
Well, depending on the resolution of the device
حسناً، حسب دقة شاشة الجهاز
we'll show the image from the appropriate Java folder.
سنعرض الصورة من مجلد جافا مناسب.
That way the image always looks sharp and crisp on the device.
وبهذه الطريقة، دائمًا ما تبدو الصورة حادة وواضحة على الجهاز.
So, I'm sure you have a lot of unanswered questions
لذلك، أنني متأكد أنك لديك الكثير من الأسئلة التي لم تتم الإجابة عنها
as to why the images are structured this way.
مثل لماذا يتم إنشاء الصور بهذه الطريقة.
And don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
This is definitely expected.
يُعد ذلك متوقعًا بالتأكيد.
We'll go more into detail about these answers in the next video.
سنقدم المزيد من التفاصيل حول هذه الإجابات في الفيديو التالي.